This is your last bonus.
Aki-sama's birthday is the 24th of this month.
Christmas Eve!
She'll be really happy if
you celebrate it with her.
I see! Thank you, Master! No, my goddess!
Also...
I'm going to stop making contact
with you like this.
Huh?
#6 "Our Second Date"
My birfdayth?
I was born in January,
but I was wondering when you were born.
Huh... When do you think it is?
Uh... I dunno. I'm not really
good at guessing. Maybe summer?
Well, you're way off. It's December 24th.
She's so cute when she makes faces
like that. Just like when we were kids.
Huh... So you were born on Christmas Eve.
Let me celebrate that day with you, then.
That's not a bad proposal
coming from you for once.
Is that an okay? Yes! I did it, Master!
Aki-sama, here's your extra mochi.
Right. That was the agreement.
She's so thorough.
Anyway, I can't get any more help from Master.
I'll have to think up these
Christmas plans myself.
Here's Our
Recommended
Christmas Course!
Cute Christmas Fashion
and Accessories ♥
Our Best Christmas Date
Report!!
But there are just too many options...
S-Say, Chinatsu.
Hm?
If you were going on a Christmas
date, what would you like to do?
A Christmas date?
Why, go to a castle, of course!
What?
I'd rent out a whole castle,
cosplay as a princess, and dance!
I'm talking about something
rooted in reality here.
Oh. Then I guess I could
compromise and settle for
dinner at a hotel with an ocean view.
You middle school girls sure expect a lot.
What's this? Are you talking about dates?
Mom! You've had a Christmas
dinner with Dad before, right?
I have! But it was so troublesome
because they accidentally
brought out a kids' lunch for me.
What the heck?
And then they brought out Hamburg steak.
Yeah?
Yeah, my bad for even
asking you two in the first place.
I couldn't eat all of it.
Did you, though?
Yeah. My stomach was so full.
Oh. Hey, by the way, Onii-chan.
Since we're talking about Christmas,
Mom did a lottery in the
shopping district today and...
When all else fails...
I'll have to rely on the bible of a million girls,
as well as my own... Rose-eyed Steroid!
Rose-eyed Steroid
Hanano Rabuko
Vvoooorrrr
That's
fine,
because
you're
safe.
...
was
ruined.
Christmases in 2D are so overshadowed by
other incidents that it's not Christmas at all!
Maybe I should just buy some new outfits.
What do you think?
I'm sure you'd look amazing
in any of them, Aki-sama.
A perfect place for a Christmas date?
Shh! Not so loud!
S-Sorry. Is this for you and Adagaki-san?
Yeah...
Aw, that sounds like fun.
I've been researching a lot,
but nothing's really speaking to me.
Well, I know plenty of
exceptional restaurants.
Italian "Buono"
The fresh pasta at this
Italian place is amazing,
and this place has great
super-soft Hamburg steak.
Oh, and you need a reservation
for the pancakes at this café,
but they're super yummy!
You have to try them once before you die!
R-Right...
Welcome.
Thank you very much.
Just five more minutes...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What?
Oh, just... I guess you really did decide
against cosplaying as Hada Pure.
Th-That was just Yoshino's mistake!
I know. You told me before.
Just forget about it already!
Right this second! Sooner, if you can!
So, what are we going to do today?
I couldn't think of anything too creative,
so sorry it's a rehash of last time, but...
No zombies?
No zombies.
Well, okay, then.
Sorry, but I didn't rent out the whole theater.
I guess I can't expect too much.
Hey.
You're too close.
I bought one extra seat to
the side again, just in case,
but I doubt it'll be any different...
I mean, I'm not going to tell you
not to sit next to me if we're dating.
Pochi! Come here!
I can't even concentrate...
The smell of popcorn and
the actors' cheesy lines
are messing with my brain.
But I should try not to forget...
that the feelings we feel right
now actually made us happy.
They weren't a lie.
Yoshino.
It's Christmas. Why do you look so gloomy?
I don't. And Christmas doesn't concern me.
Well, I guess you're right.
Here.
What's this?
Work, you dummy. Well, see you later.
Th-That wasn't fair...
I let my guard down because
you said there were no zombies,
but it was a story about
an old man and animals.
I just...
This time, she's crying because
she was moved to tears.
Okay, okay. Just calm down.
I have reservations at a café nearby.
A café?
What's it like?
I guess they serve pancakes.
The Sweets General recommended
it to me, so it should be good.
It should be around here somewhere...
It's on the second floor
of a building with a roof.
Could it be that place?
What?!
Um... Is everything oka—
My shop!
Oh... That fire this morning
must've been at this café.
I guess so. It was really good, too.
Poor guy.
I guess I now belong in
the 2D world of incidents.
W-We'll just have to go somewhere else.
Yeah.
I'm very sorry.
We are currently...
We apologize for the wait.
Curse you, Christmas...
It's fine. This is just a
bad time to go anywhere.
We can give up for today, and—
No, Adagaki-san!
We mustn't give up so easily!
Do you have any idea just how
much research I did for this day?
So for you to tell me give up so easily...
I can't let that slide, even if it's you!
Do you understand?!
O-Okay, fine. Jeez.
What are we going to do, then?
Somewhere else that's nearby,
where we can eat and rest...
Want to come over to my place?
Are you sure your family
will be okay with this?
Yeah, it's fine. I'm sure they'll
welcome you with open arms.
Just like when Master and
Fujinomiya-san came over...
Go on, eat up. We've got
chicken and cake ready for you.
What?! Onii-chan finally lucked out?!
Actually, they might be a bit annoying...
M-Maybe it'll be okay...
It's fine. We're already here,
so I'll accept your invitation.
They might make a big fuss
at first... but they won't bite.
Do you have a ferocious dog or something?
I'm home!
Huh?
H-Hang on one second.
Wait, no one's here. That can't be right...
I'm going to the hot springs with Mom!
It's the thing Mom won in the lottery!
~Chinatsu~
Your dad is on a business trip until tomorrow.
Too bad we all couldn't go together.
-Mom-
It's the thing Mom won in the lottery!
Your dad is on a business trip until tomorrow.
Too bad we all couldn't go together.
I-I didn't hear anything about this!
Since we're talking about Christmas,
Mom did a lottery in the
shopping district today and...
That's what she meant!
Um, Makabe?
Is your family not home?
Um, uh, well...
What's this?
This means...
Basically, this means we're
completely alone together!
Joyeux Noel.
So yummy!
To think that I get to spend Christmas
with my adorable little sister...
I'm so blessed!
Stop being so dramatic.
You're embarrassing me.
Here. Your present.
This is...
I'm happy that I get to spend
Christmas with you, too.
M-Muriel... I'm so glad to be alive!
Oh, and here's a list of circles
I want you to visit.
This one's super popular right now.
Huh?
You're going to Japon again at
the end of the year, aren't you?
S-So what you're saying is...
Will you go to the huge year-end
doujinshi event for me?
Of course I will!
Leave this to your big brother!
Yay!
I'm going to the hot springs with Mom!
It's the thing Mom won in the lottery!
~Chinatsu~
Your dad is on a business trip until tomorrow.
Too bad we all couldn't go together.
-Mom-
Is this some kind of trap?!
Did I just leap into a wolf's den?
Does she think I did this on purpose?
No! This is a misunderstanding!
Um—
C-Calm down. You'll be finished if
you panic and show him weakness.
Don't be hasty! You won't be convincing
at all if you're acting suspicious!
W-Well, I guess if they
aren't here, they aren't here.
I mean, we just stopped by to have some tea.
This is no problem at all.
Or what? Did you have
some ulterior motive in mind?
L-Like hell I did!
In that case, Makabe Masamune-kun,
could I have some tea, please?
Yeah, yeah.
Damn it! I feel like I lost somehow!
Anyway, tea. Where are the tea leaves?
Maa-kun, do you want some snacks?
Want some roll cake?
I made a parfait! Want some?
Are there only snacks in this whole household?
Tea leaves, please!
I will even accept tea bags!
Hey. Can't you even make tea quietly?
Oh, er... I was just looking for the tea.
And you can't find it. I figured as much.
Whatever. You can just get some cups out.
I'll help you look for the tea.
Sorry...
Huh... I guess she can be pretty nice.
Say, Makabe.
Yeah?
We were supposed to eat pancakes today, right?
For Meals or Dessert!
Fluffy and Delicious!
You can make
them with water
1. Mix eggs and milk in a bowl.
Next, pour in the pancake mix and
stir well.
2. Make sure the frying pan is heated.
Put in a little bit of oil, and then
pour in the batter.
3. Fry them on low heat for 3 minutes,
flip them over, and fry them
for another 2 minutes.
First we add the powder to some milk and eggs...
I found them both in your fridge.
Once the batter is mixed, you just fry
them in the frying pan... apparently.
That side's done. Better flip it over now.
All right... Hup!
Adagaki-san...
Oh, you're so helpless.
Hup!
Makabe...
Well... we managed to make some.
We never did find the tea, though.
Well, we found a can of
hot cocoa, so it's fine.
Let's eat.
I honestly wanted sugar-free...
Hot cocoa and pancakes... Not bad.
But she seems happy, so it's fine.
Here. Open wide.
Oh? What's wrong? Did that get to you?
This is nothing, right?
You're still mad about earlier?
I don't know. Am I?
Everyone always says I'm sadistic,
but you're far more sadistic than me.
I felt something weird there just now.
The flavor's definitely lacking something.
You didn't add enough toppings!
Huh? Hey, wait!
This is way too much...
Why? I think it's suitable for you.
Suitable for me?
What the heck do you know about me?
Oh, that's right.
I saw vanilla ice cream in the freezer—
Adagaki-san.
Come with me for a sec.
Wha—
What's with you all of a sudden, Makabe?!
This is my room.
That, too.
No way...
You still had this?
No...
No! That's not the point, Aki-chan!
Masamune?
It's true that I'm the fat little Masamune
you knew eight years ago.
But I wanted to change from that,
and that's how I became who I am now.
So it's a bit hard for me when someone
wants me to go back to that.
Even if it was all a misunderstanding,
I can't imagine wanting to be my old self.
W-Wait...
Am I worthless... the way I am now?
Wai—
Ow...
I...
Makabe?
Sorry!
Excuse me a sec.
What?
What the hell am I doing?
Where the heck did Makabe go?
Honestly, what's his problem?
First he invites me over,
and then he just disappears!
Messages
Makabe Masamune
Edit
Okay.
In the 2nd floor
bathroom RN
My stomach hurts so much,
I can't move
There's a present for you downstairs
in my coat pocket
Messages
Makabe Masamune
Edit
There's a present for you downstairs
in my coat pocket
Please just take that and
leave for today
I'm really sorry
Also, Happy Birthday
A present?
Is this it?
I'm not sure if I should be grateful that my
phone was in my butt pocket or not...
But seriously, I'm in so much pain.
Were the loli hag's ingredients
rotten or something?
Okay.
Take care.
Cruel Princess
No, that's not it.
The last time I had a stomachache,
I didn't break out in hives like this.
They started appearing when...
I can't touch Adagaki Aki.
Welcome home, Aki-sama.
Why are you dressed like that?
The master is having a Christmas party.
I slipped away from bingo duty.
I see. Well, good work.
Was your date not fun?
Th-That's not true!
That's not true...
That's not true, but...
Say, Yoshino.
Could it be that I have no
appeal as a woman at all?
You have plenty of appeal, Aki-sama.
No, forget it! Never mind! It's nothing!
They look just like Sean and Lancelot.
Those memories are irreplaceable to me.
Don't you feel the same way?
That's what I thought, at least...
I'm going to get revenge
on that woman!!
What did that mean?